trtworld.com 2016-06-23

# Privacy Policy | TRT World

TRT aims to establish a safe and enjoyable environment for our users by keeping your personal information confidential while using the TRT services. TRT is committed to keeping your personal information safe. When such information is provided, we are legally obliged to use your information with all laws including the Constitution of the Republic of Turkey. Links to other Websites TRT contains hyperlinks to other websites operated by third party companies. These third party companies have their own privacy policies that we urge you to review. TRT does not hold any responsibility for the privacy practices of such third party websites and your use of such websites is at your own risk. Personal Information  

## 1.1 Collection of Personal Information

When you access or become a member of the TRT services, your personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone or mobile number or date of birth will be requested depending on the activity. By doing so you enable TRT to give you access to the activities you’ve selected. If you choose to not give personal information certain services may not be available to you.   

## 1.2 Use of Personal Information

TRT collects your personal information to create a better platform for our users. Your personal information helps us provide better customer service, perform research and analysis to improve our products, services and technology, and to customize a browser to our users interest.   

## 1.3 Sharing Your Personal Information

TRT does not share your personal information with outside parties, except if stated otherwise in this privacy policy. Your personal information may be shared among our corporate group including our subsidiaries and groups, other TRT channels, and other entities who cooperate with TRT channels, all of who may use your information for the purposes stated in this privacy policy.   

## 1.4 Accessing Your Personal Information

If you would like to change any personal information that you have already provided us with, you can visit your account properties and make the changes of your choice.   

## 1.5 Security of Personal Information

The security of your personal information is very important to us, which makes us strive to keep all your information given to us confidential. Security program software’s may be used to keep your information secure, however no method of transmissions over the internet or methods of electronic security is 100% secure, therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security.   

## Web Browser Cookies

Cookies are created when you use your browser to visit a website that uses cookies to keep track of your movements within the site, help you resume where you left off, remember your registered login, theme selection, preferences, and other customization functions. The website stores a corresponding file (with same ID tag) to the one they set in your browser and in this file they can track and keep information on your movements within the site and any information you may have voluntarily given while visiting the website, such as email address. On the TRT website, cookies will record information about your online preferences and allow us to tailor our websites to your interests. Information supplied by cookies can help us analyze the profile of our visitors and help us provide you with a better user experience. TRT uses this information to provide better services for its users.   

## Applications on Devices

When you download TRT applications on any device, information may be accessed or stored. This is used in a similar way to a web browser cookie. Your web browser or device may also provide the TRT with information about your device, such as a device identifier or IP address.   

## Updates and Changes of The Privacy Policy

TRT is entitled to amend or update its privacy policy at anytime. It is the users’ responsibility to check whether the terms are amended or updated. Therefore, you accept all up-to-date usage conditions as long as you continue using the related language portals. If you do not accept the amended or updated terms please do not use the website any longer.
